SADIMA MAHARJAN

04234324234 |

npsadimamaharjan@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/sadima-maharjan

Career Profile

I am a disciplined and enthusiastic individual eager to work in front-end web development with a desire to learn and grow in a collaborative environment. I have over two years of experience as a project manager in a leading telecommunication company where I have undertaken and delivered various responsibilities as an in-house web developer, project manager and IT support.

Professional Experience

Telstra Partner-Truetel Solutions Pty Ltd., Sunshine West, Victoria

Project Manager and IT Support, September 2020 – August 2022

- Developed and implemented front-end code using HTML, CSS, JavaScript to meet business requirements.
- Performed regular site maintenance including updates, backups, and security checks.
- As a project manager, I have managed projects that included installing NBN and telephone systems for Telstra small business customers.
- I enabled various small businesses to transition to Cloud PBX technology and resolve any complications during the transition.
- I was responsible for all the back-end work for projects such as ordering hardware, programming handsets, installation, invoicing, billing, updating CRM, record keeping and documentation.
- I trained the interns to resolve concerns related to hardware and software functionality.

Truetel Solutions Pty Ltd., Sunshine West, Victoria

Intern, June 2020 - September 2020

- Employed programming language skills (Javascript, CSS, HTML) to create user-oriented websites.
- Performed unit testing to ensure optimal browser compatibility.
- Conduct periodic audits of websites and customer databases to determine security violations and inefficiencies.
- Implemented responsive design techniques so the site could be viewed on any device without issue.

Access Keys Pvt Ltd, Kathmandu, Nepal

Junior Web Designer, April 2014 - April 2015

- Developed a strong understanding of aesthetic and design principles.
- Improved coding skills while designing cross browser, responsive websites.

- Enhanced teamwork skills by communicating with team leader and aiding new design interns.
- Completed design work within deadline with prioritisation and effective organisation.

Education

Professional Year Business Program November 2019- May 2020

Performance Education, Melbourne

Master of Information Technology November 2017- June 2019

La Trobe University, Melbourne

Bachelor of Computer Engineering November 2009- April 2013

Kathmandu Engineering College, Kathmandu, Nepal.

Extra-Curricular Activities

- Won COSBOA (The Council of Small Business Australia) Innovation Games sponsored by Energy Australia held on 15th May 2019, where I collaborated in a team of 8 students from Australia along with mentors and representatives of Energy Australia.
- Conducted market research with international students of different universities in a team of six in Study
 Melbourne LIVE Project funded by Victorian Government held from November 2018 to December 2018 to solve a real business problem.

Referees

Jack Chowdhury, Managing Director, Truetel Solutions Pvt. Ltd., 0477888141, jack.chowdhury@truetel.com.au Brenda Moore, General Manager, Truetel Solutions Pvt. Ltd., 0477555310, brenda.moore@truetel.com.au